A Guide to the Population Council records, Central Files, Accession 2, RG 2, Series 1 to Series 4 FA432
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Accession 2, Central Files, 1957-1983; bulk; 2; 286 Cubic Feet
  - Administration File, 3; 110.4 Cubic Feet Boxes 204-479.
    - Montague, Joel - Country File - Algeria - Bourcier de Carbon, 1971-1973 (Box 324, Folder 3087)
    - Montague, Joel - Country File - Algeria - Algeria de Sousa, 1971 (Box 324, Folder 3088)
    - Montague, Joel - Country File - Algeria - Algeria De Saadas, 1971 (Box 324, Folder 3089)
    - Montague, Joel - Country File - Algeria - Demographic Statistical Research; Population Projections, 1970-1972 (Box 324, Folder 3090)
    - Montague, Joel - Country File - Libya - General Information, 1970-1974 (Box 324, Folder 3091)
    - Montague, Joel - Country File - Oman - General, 1973-1974 (Box 324, Folder 3092)
    - Montague, Joel - Country File - Oman - Reports, 1973 (Box 324, Folder 3093)
    - Montague, Joel - Country File - Saudia Arabia - General Information, 1973-1975 (Box 324, Folder 3094)
    - Montague, Joel - Country File - Qatar - General Information, 1972-1973 (Box 324, Folder 3095)
    - Montague, Joel - Country File - Syria - General Information, 1973-1974 (Box 325, Folder 3096)
    - Montague, Joel - Country File - Yemen - General Information, 1970-1975 (Box 325, Folder 3097)
    - Montague, Joel - Country File - Kuwait - General Information, 1972-1975 (Box 325, Folder 3098)
    - Montague, Joel - Country File - Management - UNFPA Management Conference, 1971-1972 (Box 325, Folder 3099)
    - Montague, Joel - Country File - Management - Population Services, Inc. (PSI), "A PSI Pre-Launch Social Marketing Survey", 1972 (Box 325, Folder 3100)
    - Montague, Joel - Country File - Management - Summerskill Report, 1971-1972 (Box 325, Folder 3101)
    - Montague, Joel - Country File - Management - Thailand, 1972 (Box 325, Folder 3102)
    - Montague, Joel - Country File - Management - University of North Carolina - E.S. Trainer, 1973 (Box 325, Folder 3103)
    - Montague, Joel - Country File - Management - Washington University, 1972 (Box 325, Folder 3104)
    - Montague, Joel - Country File - Management - Zaltman, Gerald, 1972 (Box 325, Folder 3105)
    - Montague, Joel - Country File - Management - Management Services for Health (MSH), 1971-1974 (Box 326, Folder 3106)
    - Montague, Joel - Country File - Management - McKinney and Co., 1971-1972 (Box 326, Folder 3107)
    - Montague, Joel - Country File - Management - Miscellaneous Articles, 1974 (Box 326, Folder 3108)
    - Montague, Joel - Country File - Management - Government Affairs Institute - John P. Scottice, 1973-1974 (Box 326, Folder 3109)
    - Montague, Joel - Country File - Management - Iran, 1969-1973 (Box 326, Folder 3110)
    - Montague, Joel - Country File - Management - Garth Jones, 1973 (Box 326, Folder 3111)
    - Montague, Joel - Country File - Management - Keeny Parker, 1971 (Box 326, Folder 3112)
    - Montague, Joel - Country File - Management - David Korten, 1975 (Box 326, Folder 3113)
    - Montague, Joel - Country File - Management - Arthur D. Little Proposal, 1971-1972 (Box 326, Folder 3114)
    - Montague, Joel - Country File - Management - Macro Systems, Inc., New York, 1971-1972 (Box 326, Folder 3115)
    - Montague, Joel - Country File - Management Analysis Center, Inc. (MAC), California, 1971-1972 (Box 326, Folder 3116)
    - Montague, Joel - Country File - Technical Assistance Division (TAD) - International Committee on the Management of Population Programs (ICOMP), 1974-1975 (Box 327, Folder 3117)
    - Montague, Joel - Country File - Management - Harvard University - David Korten, 1973-1975 (Box 327, Folder 3118)
    - Montague, Joel - Country File - Management - Letters, Memos and Reports, 1971-1974 (Box 327, Folder 3119)
    - Montague, Joel - Country File - Management - Position Paper, 1971-1972 (Box 327, Folder 3120)
    - Montague, Joel - Country File - Management - PC Summary Paper, 1972 (Box 327, Folder 3121)
    - Montague, Joel - Country File - Management Proposals, 1971-1972 (Box 327, Folder 3122)
    - Montague, Joel - Country File - Association of University Programs in Health Administration (AUPHA) - G. L. Filerman, 1973 (Box 327, Folder 3123)
    - Montague, Joel - Country File - Management - Booz Allen, 1972 (Box 327, Folder 3124)
    - Montague, Joel - Country File - Management - International Committee on Management of Population Programs (ICOMP), 1973-1974 (Box 327, Folder 3125)
    - Montague, Joel - Country File - Management - Ford Foundation, 1971-1972 (Box 328, Folder 3126)
    - Montague, Joel - Country File - Niger, 1973 (Box 328, Folder 3127)
    - Montague, Joel - Country File - Nigeria - Reports, 1970-1975 (Box 328, Folder 3128)
    - Montague, Joel - Country File - Nigeria - Zuma Memorial Hospital - General, 1968-1975 (Box 328, Folder 3129)
    - Montague, Joel - Country File - Nigeria - Zuma Memorial Hospital - Information and Reports, 1972-1974 (Box 328, Folder 3130)
    - Montague, Joel - Country File - Nigeria - Zuma Memorial Hospital - Dr. Xto Okojie, 1971-1975 (Box 328, Folder 3131)
    - Montague, Joel - Country File - University of Nigeria, 1972-1975 (Box 329, Folder 3132)
    - Montague, Joel - Country File - Nigeria, 1972-1975 (Box 329, Folder 3133)
    - Montague, Joel - Country File - Nigeria - Abortion Symposium, 1974-1975 (Box 329, Folder 3134)
    - Montague, Joel - Country File -Nigeria - Lagos - Postpartum Trip to Nigeria - Mr. Sobovejo, 1975 (Box 329, Folder 3135)
    - Montague, Joel - Country File - Rwanda, 1973 (Box 329, Folder 3136)
    - Montague, Joel - Country File - Senegal, 1968-1975 (Box 329, Folder 3137)
    - Montague, Joel - Country File - Indonesia - Personnel - John Laing, 1973-1975 (Box 330, Folder 3138)
    - Montague, Joel - Country File - Indonesia - Personnel - Alden Speare, Jr., 1974 (Box 330, Folder 3139)
    - Montague, Joel - Country File - Indonesia - Personnel - Gavin Jones, 1972-1974 (Box 330, Folder 3140)
    - Montague, Joel - Country File - Indonesia - Personnel - Robert Melton, 1973-1975 (Box 330, Folder 3141)
    - Montague, Joel - Country File - Indonesia - Personnel - Jeremiah Sullivan, 1973-1974 (Box 330, Folder 3142)
    - Montague, Joel - Country File - Indonesia - Personnel - House File, 1974-1976 (Box 330, Folder 3143)
    - Montague, Joel - Country File - Indonesia: Personnel - Paul Mackenzie, 1974 (Box 330, Folder 3144)
    - Montague, Joel - Country File - Indonesia - Indonesia Office - General People File, 1971-1976 (Box 330, Folder 3145)
    - Montague, Joel - Country File - Indonesia - Other Programs - AID, 1972-1975 (Box 330, Folder 3146)
    - Montague, Joel - Country File - Indonesia: Other Programs - BKKBN-IUD Raw Materials, 1974-1975 (Box 330, Folder 3147)
    - Montague, Joel - Country File - Indonesia - Other Programs - Biomedical, 1974 (Box 330, Folder 3148)
    - Montague, Joel - Country File - Indonesia - Other Programs - New Proposals, 1974-1975 (Box 330, Folder 3149)
    - Montague, Joel - Country File - Indonesia - Other Programs - Miscellaneous, 1973-1976 (Box 330, Folder 3150)
    - Montague, Joel - Country File - Indonesia - Population Council Agreement, 1973-1976 (Box 330, Folder 3151)
    - Montague, Joel - Country File - Indonesia - Miscellaneous Requests, 1974 (Box 330, Folder 3152)
    - Montague, Joel - Country File - Indonesia - Information - General, 1972-1975 (Box 330, Folder 3153)
    - Montague, Joel - Country File - Indonesia - Information Program, 1973-1975 (Box 331, Folder 3154)
    - Montague, Joel - Country File - Korea - Projects - General Grants Review by Worth, 1975 January 10 (Box 331, Folder 3155)
    - Montague, Joel - Country File - Korea - Other Council Activities - New Proposals, 1974-1976 (Box 331, Folder 3156)
    - Montague, Joel - Country File - Korea - Other Council Activities - Korea Evaluation, 1971-1974 (Box 331, Folder 3157)
    - Montague, Joel - Country File - Korea - Other Council Activities - General, 1975 (Box 331, Folder 3158)
    - Montague, Joel - Country File - Korea - Other Council Activites - Demographic Activities, 1973-1975 (Box 331, Folder 3159)
    - Montague, Joel - Country File - Korea - Other Council Activities - Working File - Korea Trip, 1972 (Box 331, Folder 3160)
    - Montague, Joel - Country File - Korea - Other Council Activities - TCU (Copper T), 1971-1973 (Box 331, Folder 3161)
    - Montague, Joel - Country File - International Comm. for Applied Research for Population (ICARP), 1973-1976 (Box 331, Folder 3162)
    - Montague, Joel - Country File - Korea: Other Council Activities - Research and Evaluation, 1974 (Box 331, Folder 3163)
    - Montague, Joel - Country File - Korea - Other Council Activities - Sterilization Project in Korea, 1974-1975 (Box 331, Folder 3164)
    - Montague, Joel - Country File - Korea - Other Council Activities - Seoul National University - Public Health Proposal, 1974 (Box 331, Folder 3165)
    - Montague, Joel - Country File - Korea - Fellowship and Travel Grants, 1971-1974 (Box 331, Folder 3166)
    - Montague, Joel - Country File - Korea - Korean Office, 1971-1976 (Box 331, Folder 3167)
    - Montague, Joel - Country File - Korea - Other Programs - AID, 1970-1975 (Box 332, Folder 3168)
    - Montague, Joel - Country File - Korea - Other Programs - International Planned Parenthood Federation (IPPF), 1970 (Box 332, Folder 3169)
    - Montague, Joel - Country File - Korea - Other Programs - United Nations Fund for Population Activites (UNFPA), 1972-1976 (Box 332, Folder 3170)
    - Montague, Joel - Country File - Korea - Other Programs - Miscellaneous, 1972-1976 (Box 332, Folder 3171)
    - Montague, Joel - Country File - Korea - Personnel - Donaldson, 1974-1975 (Box 332, Folder 3172)
    - Montague, Joel - Country File - Korea - Personnel - Watson, 1973-1974 (Box 332, Folder 3173)
    - Montague, Joel - Country File - Korea - Personnel - Worth, 1971-1975 (Box 332, Folder 3174)
    - Montague, Joel - Country File - Korea - Personnel - Recruitment, 1973-1975 (Box 332, Folder 3175)
    - Montague, Joel - Country File - Korea - Information - General, 1972-1976 (Box 332, Folder 3176)
    - Montague, Joel - Country File - Korea - Information - Political/Policy, 1972-1974 (Box 332, Folder 3177)
    - Montague, Joel - Country File - Korea - Information - Program, 1971-1975 (Box 333, Folder 3178)
    - Montague, Joel - Country File - Laos - Information - General, 1971-1974 (Box 333, Folder 3179)
    - Montague, Joel - Country File - Laos - Information - Reports, 1970-1972 (Box 333, Folder 3180)
    - Montague, Joel - Country File - Malaysia - Other Programs - International Planned Parenthood Federation (IPPF), 1971 (Box 333, Folder 3181)
    - Montague, Joel - Country File - Malaysia - Other Programs - NFPA - National Family Planning Board, 1970-1975 (Box 333, Folder 3182)
    - Montague, Joel - Country File - Malaysia - Other Programs - Proposals, 1973 (Box 333, Folder 3183)
    - Montague, Joel - Country File - Malaysia - Other Programs - Miscellaneous, 1975 (Box 333, Folder 3184)
    - Montague, Joel - Country File - Malaysia - Information - Political/Policy, 1970-1974 (Box 333, Folder 3185)
    - Montague, Joel - Country File - Malaysia - Information - Program, 1972-1975 (Box 333, Folder 3186)
    - Montague, Joel - Country File - Malaysia - Information - General, 1972-1975 (Box 333, Folder 3187)
    - Montague, Joel - Country File - Malaysia - Information - Reports and Analysis, 1970-1974 (Box 333, Folder 3188)
    - Montague, Joel - Country File - Malaysia - Miscellaneous Requests, 1968-1974 (Box 333, Folder 3189)
    - Montague, Joel - Country File - Miscellaneous Countries, 1972-1974 (Box 333, Folder 3190)
    - Montague, Joel - Country File - New Guinea, 1972-1974 (Box 333, Folder 3191)
    - Montague, Joel - Country File - Nepal, 1970-1974 (Box 334, Folder 3192)
    - Montague, Joel - Country File - North Vietnam, 1973-1975 (Box 334, Folder 3193)
    - Montague, Joel - Country File - Philippines - Other Council Activities - International Institute of Rural Reconstruction (IIRR) Project, 1971-1974 (Box 334, Folder 3194)
    - Montague, Joel - Country File - Philippines - Other Council Activities - International Comm. for Applied Research for Population (ICARP), 1974-1975 (Box 334, Folder 3195)
    - Montague, Joel - Country File - Philippines - Other Council Activities - Demography, 1973-1974 (Box 334, Folder 3196)
    - Montague, Joel - Country File - Philippines - Other Council Activities - Field Postpartum, 1973-1975 (Box 334, Folder 3197)
    - Montague, Joel - Country File - Philippines - Other Council Activities - IUDs, 1975 (Box 334, Folder 3198)
    - Montague, Joel - Country File - Philippines - Other Council Activities - Demographic, 1974 (Box 334, Folder 3199)
    - Montague, Joel - Country File - Philippines - Other Programs - United Nations Fund for Population Activities (UNFPA), 1972-1975 (Box 334, Folder 3200)
    - Montague, Joel - Country File - Philippines - Other Programs - World Bank, 1972 (Box 334, Folder 3201)
    - Montague, Joel - Country File - Philippines - Other Programs - AID/ea-8, 1968-1969 (Box 334, Folder 3202)
    - Montague, Joel - Country File - Philippines - Other Programs - AID, 1975 (Box 334, Folder 3203)
    - Montague, Joel - Country File - Philippines - Other Programs - Miscellaneous, 1973-1976 (Box 334, Folder 3204)
    - Montague, Joel - Country File - Philippines - Personnel - John Laing, 1974-1976 (Box 334, Folder 3205)
    - Montague, Joel - Country File - Philippines - Personnel - Peter Miller, 1975 (Box 334, Folder 3206)
    - Montague, Joel - Country File - Philippines - Personnel - James Phillips, 1973-1974 (Box 334, Folder 3207)
    - Montague, Joel - Country File - Philippines - Personnel - Bill Van Wie, 1973-1976 (Box 334, Folder 3208)
    - Montague, Joel - Country File - Philippines - Office, 1975 (Box 334, Folder 3209)
    - Montague, Joel - Country File - Philippines - PC Agreement, 1973-1974 (Box 334, Folder 3210)
    - Montague, Joel - Country File - Philippines - Information - Programs, 1972-1975 (Box 335, Folder 3211)
    - Montague, Joel - Country File - Philippines - Information - Political/Policy, 1972-1975 (Box 335, Folder 3212)
    - Montague, Joel - Country File - Philippines - Information - General, 1970-1976 (Box 335, Folder 3213)
    - Montague, Joel - Country File - Philippines - Miscellaneous Requests, 1971-1976 (Box 335, Folder 3214)
    - Montague, Joel - Country File - Singapore - Information - General, 1973-1976 (Box 335, Folder 3215)
    - Montague, Joel - Country File - Singapore - James Fawcett, 1974-1975 (Box 336, Folder 3216)
    - Montague, Joel - Country File - Singapore - Information - Program, 1968-1975 (Box 336, Folder 3217)
    - Montague, Joel - Country File - Singapore - Information - Political/Policy, 1971-1975 (Box 336, Folder 3218)
    - Montague, Joel - Country File - Singapore - Proposals, 1970-1973 (Box 336, Folder 3219)
    - Montague, Joel - Country File - Singapore - Reports, 1972-1975 (Box 336, Folder 3219A)
    - Montague, Joel - Country File - Taiwan - Other Council Activities - Babb's Review of all Joint Commission on Rural Reconstruction (JCRR) grants still active, 1975 August (Box 336, Folder 3220)
    - Montague, Joel - Country File - Taiwan - Other Council Activities - International Comm. for Applied Research for Population (ICARP), 1973-1975 (Box 336, Folder 3221)
    - Montague, Joel - Country File - Taiwan - Other Council Activities - Biomedical, 1972-1973 (Box 336, Folder 3222)
    - Montague, Joel - Country File - Taiwan - Other Council Activities - General, 1974-1976 (Box 336, Folder 3223)
    - Montague, Joel - Country File - Taiwan - Other Council Activities - Demographic, 1971-1975 (Box 336, Folder 3224)
    - Montague, Joel - Country File - Taiwan - Other Council Activities - Reports, 1972-1975 (Box 336, Folder 3225)
    - Montague, Joel - Country File - Taiwan - Other Council Activities - New Proposals, 1974-1975 (Box 336, Folder 3226)
    - Montague, Joel - Country File - Taiwan - Fellowship and Travel Grants, 1973-1976 (Box 336, Folder 3227)
    - Montague, Joel - Country File - Taiwan - Other Programs - National Taiwan University - Institutional Development - NTU Proposal, 1974-1975 (Box 336, Folder 3228)
    - Montague, Joel - Country File - Taiwan - Other Programs - New Directions Proposal, 1974 (Box 336, Folder 3229)
    - Montague, Joel - Country File - Taiwan - Other Programs - Miscellaneous, 1972-1975 (Box 337, Folder 3230)
    - Montague, Joel - Country File - Taiwan - Other Programs - Pathfinder, 1972-1974 (Box 337, Folder 3231)
    - Montague, Joel - Country File - Tawain - Other Programs - Planned Parenthood - Maternity and Child Health Demonstration Project (Box 337, Folder 3232)
    - Montague, Joel - Country File - Taiwan - Office, 1972-1975 (Box 337, Folder 3233)
    - Montague, Joel - Country File - Taiwan - Personnel - S.M. Keeny, 1973-1976 (Box 337, Folder 3234)
    - Montague, Joel - Country File - Taiwan - Personnel - George P. Cernada, 1973-1975 (Box 337, Folder 3235)
    - Montague, Joel - Country File - Taiwan - Personnel - Eleanor Cernada, 1972-1974 (Box 337, Folder 3236)
    - Montague, Joel - Country File - Taiwan - Miscellaneous Requests, 1974-1975 (Box 337, Folder 3237)
    - Montague, Joel - Country File - Bangladesh - Information - General, 1975-1976 (Box 337, Folder 3238)
    - Montague, Joel - Country File - Bangladesh - Information - General, 1972-1974 (Box 338, Folder 3239)
    - Montague, Joel - Country File - Bangladesh: Information - Political/Policy, 1974 (Box 338, Folder 3240)
    - Montague, Joel - Country File - Bangladesh: Information - Program, 1974 (Box 338, Folder 3241)
    - Montague, Joel - Country File - Bangladesh - Other Programs - Ford Foundation, 1974-1975 (Box 338, Folder 3242)
    - Montague, Joel - Country File - Bangladesh: Other Programs - United Nations Fund for Population Activities (UNFPA), 1972-1974 (Box 338, Folder 3243)
    - Montague, Joel - Country File - Bangladesh - Other Programs - Proposals, 1974 (Box 338, Folder 3244)
    - Montague, Joel - Country File - Bangladesh - Personnel - Dr. Lincoln Chen, 1973-1975 (Box 338, Folder 3245)
    - Montague, Joel - Country File - Bangladesh - Personnel - Dr. Atiqur Rahman, 1973 (Box 338, Folder 3246)
    - Montague, Joel - Country File - Bangladesh - Personnel - Dr. Adaline Pendleton Satterthwaite, 1974 (Box 338, Folder 3247)
    - Montague, Joel - Country File - Burma, 1970-1974 (Box 338, Folder 3248)
    - Montague, Joel - Country File - Cambodia, 1970-1972 (Box 338, Folder 3249)
    - Montague, Joel - Country File - Ceylon - Projects by Number - T72.013C Ceylon Ministry of Health, 1971-1975 (Box 338, Folder 3250)
    - Montague, Joel - Country File - Ceylon - Fellowships, 1974 (Box 338, Folder 3251)
    - Montague, Joel - Country File - Ceylon - Other Council Activities - IUD (Colombo) Survey, 1972-1974 (Box 338, Folder 3252)
    - Montague, Joel - Country File - Ceylon - Information, 1970-1975 (Box 338, Folder 3253)
    - Montague, Joel - Country File - China - PC Activities - Monograph, 1972-1974 (Box 338, Folder 3254)
    - Montague, Joel - Country File - China - PC Activities - China Contact, 1972-1973 (Box 338, Folder 3255)
    - Montague, Joel - Country File - China - PC Activities - Proposals, 1972-1974 (Box 338, Folder 3256)
    - Montague, Joel - Country File - China - PC Activities - Chen Travel, 1972-1973 (Box 338, Folder 3257)
    - Montague, Joel - Country File - China - PC Activities - Chen Travel, 1973-1974 (Box 338, Folder 3258)
    - Montague, Joel - Country File - China - PC Activities - China Seminar, 1971-1973 (Box 339, Folder 3259)
    - Montague, Joel - Country File - China - Information - Political/Policy, 1972-1974 (Box 339, Folder 3260)
    - Montague, Joel - Country File - China - Information - Program, 1973 (Box 339, Folder 3261)
    - Montague, Joel - Country File - China - Information - General, 1970-1974 (Box 339, Folder 3262)
    - Montague, Joel - Country File - Fiji, 1970-1974 (Box 339, Folder 3263)
    - Montague, Joel - Country File - Hong Kong - Information, 1970-1975 (Box 339, Folder 3264)
    - Montague, Joel - Country File - India - Information - Meeting, 1974 October 7 (Box 339, Folder 3265)
    - Montague, Joel - Country File - India - Information - PC Reviews, 1970-1974 (Box 339, Folder 3266)
    - Montague, Joel - Country File - India - Information - Program, 1974-1975 (Box 339, Folder 3267)
    - Montague, Joel - Country File - India - Information - Political/Policy, 1973 (Box 339, Folder 3268)
    - Montague, Joel - Country File - India - Information - General, 1972-1975 (Box 339, Folder 3269)
    - Montague, Joel - Country File - India - People, 1970-1975 (Box 340, Folder 3270)
    - Montague, Joel - Country File - India - Fellowships and Travel Grants, 1974 (Box 340, Folder 3271)
    - Montague, Joel - Country File - India - B.R. Deolaliker, 1974 (Box 340, Folder 3272)
    - Montague, Joel - Country File - India - Proposals, 1973-1975 (Box 340, Folder 3273)
    - Montague, Joel - Country File - Indonesia - International Development Assocation/United Nations Fund for Population Activity (IDA/UNFPA) - Agreement, 1973-1974 (Box 340, Folder 3274)
    - Montague, Joel - Country File - Indonesia - IDA/UNFPA - Research and Evaluation, 1973-1974 (Box 340, Folder 3275)
    - Montague, Joel - Country File - Indonesia - IDA/UNFPA - General, 1973-1975 (Box 340, Folder 3276)
    - Montague, Joel - Country File - Indonesia - IDA/UNFPA - Field Post Partum (T-B, MCH-FP), 1972-1975 (Box 340, Folder 3277)
    - Montague, Joel - Country File - Indonesia - IDA/UNFPA - LEKNAS, 1973-1975 (Box 340, Folder 3278)
    - Montague, Joel - Country File - Indonesia - Other Council Activities - Demographic, 1974-1975 (Box 340, Folder 3279)
    - Montague, Joel - Country File - Indonesia - Other Council Activities - Institutional Development, 1974-1975 (Box 340, Folder 3280)
    - Montague, Joel - Country File - Indonesia - Other Council Activities - Lippes Loops - Licenses, Patents, Distribution and Manufacture, 1964-1976 (Box 340, Folder 3281)
    - Montague, Joel - Country File - Indonesia - Other Council Activities - IUD Loss of Memory File, 1975-1976 (Box 340, Folder 3282)
    - Montague, Joel - Country File - Indonesia - Fellowships and Travel Grants, 1973-1975 (Box 340, Folder 3283)
    - Montague, Joel - Country File - Lebanon - Background and Reports, 1971-1973 (Box 340, Folder 3284)
    - Montague, Joel - Country File - Lebanon - Correspondence and Memos, 1971-1975 (Box 341, Folder 3285)
    - Montague, Joel - Country File - Lebanon - American University of Beirut, 1971-1974 (Box 341, Folder 3286)
    - Montague, Joel - Country File - Lebanon - American University of Beirut - General, 1971-1973 (Box 341, Folder 3287)
    - Montague, Joel - Country File - Lebanon - General Information, 1972-1974 (Box 341, Folder 3288)
    - Montague, Joel - Country File - Egypt - Background Information and Reports, 1968-1971 (Box 341, Folder 3289)
    - Montague, Joel - Country File - Egypt - Background Information and Reports, 1969-1974 (Box 342, Folder 3290)
    - Montague, Joel - Country File - Egypt - Correspondence, 1973-1974 (Box 342, Folder 3291)
    - Montague, Joel - Country File - Egypt - Correspondence, 1971-1972 (Box 342, Folder 3292)
    - Montague, Joel - Country File - Egypt - Memos, 1970-1976 (Box 342, Folder 3293)
    - Montague, Joel - Country File - Egypt - Programs, 1971-1973 (Box 342, Folder 3294)
    - Montague, Joel - Country File - Egypt - Miscellaneous, 1969-1974 (Box 342, Folder 3295)
    - Montague, Joel - Country File - Egypt - Specific Requests, 1971-1972 (Box 342, Folder 3296)
    - Montague, Joel - Country File - Egypt - Broken Loops, 1970-1973 (Box 342, Folder 3297)